♪ ♪
♪ YOU PUT ME ON A PEDESTAL
AND TELL ME I'M THE BEST ♪
♪ ♪
♪ RAISE ME UP INTO THE SKY
UNTIL I'M SHORT OF BREATH ♪
♪ ♪
♪ FILL ME UP WITH CONFIDENCE,
I SAY WHAT'S IN MY CHEST ♪
♪ SPILL MY WORDS AND
TEAR ME DOWN UNTIL
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT ♪
♪ REARRANGE THE PIECES JUST
TO FIT ME WITH THE REST ♪
♪ BUT WHAT IF I,
WHAT IF I TRIP, ♪
♪ WHAT IF I WHAT IF I FALL ♪
♪ ♪
♪ THEN AM I THE MONSTER,
JUST LET ME KNOW ♪
♪ WHAT IF I WHAT IF I SIN, ♪
♪ ♪
♪ WHAT IF I WHAT IF I BREAK ♪
♪ THEN AM I THE MONSTER,
JUST LET ME KNOW YEAAHHH ♪
♪ I WAS 15 WHEN THE WORLD
PUT ME ON A PEDESTAL ♪
♪ I HAD BIG DREAMS OF DOING
SHOWS AND MAKING MEMORIES ♪
♪ MADE SOME BAD MOVES
TRYING TO ACT COOL UPSET
BY THEIR JEALOUSY ♪
♪ LIFTING ME UP,
LIFTING ME UP, YEAH ♪
♪ AND TEARING ME DOWN,
TEARING ME DOWN, DOWN, DOWN, ♪
♪ TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR
EVERYTHING I'VE DONE, ♪
♪ HOLDING IT AGAINST ME
LIKE YOU'RE THE HOLY ONE ♪
♪ (YEAH) ♪
♪ I HAD A CHIP ON MY
SHOULDER, HAD TO LET IT GO ♪
♪ CAUSE UNFORGIVENESS KEEPS
THEM IN CONTROL, ♪
♪ I CAME IN WITH GOOD
INTENTIONS THEN I LET IT GO ♪
♪ AND NOW I REALLY WANNA KNOW ♪
♪ WHAT IF I WHAT IF I TRIP, ♪
♪ WHAT IF I WHAT IF
I FALL, I FALL ♪
♪ THEN AM I THE MONSTER,
JUST LET ME KNOW ♪
♪ WHAT IF I WHAT IF I SIN, ♪
♪ (OHHH) ♪
♪ WHAT IF I, WHAT IF I
BREAK YEAH ♪
♪ THEN AM I THE MONSTER,
JUST LET ME KNOW ♪
♪ JUST LET ME KNOW ♪
♪ (VOCALIZING) ♪
♪ (PLEASE DON'T LET ME FALL) ♪
♪ ♪